Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Outro music.
get up
That just now in the second time
I was hoping my story
It's Volkssort
I am actually all going on
your life
I am really watching you
Homelessness
My new Beautiful
Twilight
Disney
Though, well, look
Whatever.
I displaced
The systems
There are only
The situation
Remember what you got, it's a blast over!
I love you!
Arielle, that's good. So tasty. I love snow cones.
You're mine! Flame magic, spiral flame!
Snow magic! I swallowed the unfriing rays!
Finally, we did it! Team G wins the match!
What?
While both crystals on the fields have been shattered, Team E's was destroyed seconds before Team G's.
Thank goodness. Longris and Seike pulled it off and managed to defeat you.
Dear me, did I miss anything?
I can't believe those guys beat us! We need more focus!
I guess I still can't hold a candle to my big brother.
What horrific magic power!
But who could be conjuring it?
What's going on out there?
There! Do you understand now? You can never beat me!
Charming now!
Con-creation magic! Fluffy Sheep Cushion to the rescue!
Disappear.
Go on, take one more step toward him.
But you should know that the second you do, you're dead.
Huh?
There's something wrong with you!
The match was already over!
You Black Bulls may be doing better than expected, but you're still worthless underlings.
You think you can take the Vice-Captain of the Golden Dawn?
Your Frank has nothing to do with this!
All we care about is protecting our friend!
Perhaps your friend shouldn't be so weak.
That's quite enough.
I appreciate the fact that you didn't pull your punches while fighting against your brother.
But trying to kill a fellow magic knight is something else altogether, and it has no place in this tournament.
These are grave injuries. I'll handle them.
Thanks, Dr. Owen.
Water recovery magic.
Kuala operation.
Can you heal him?
I'll do everything within my power.
See your friend?
He's completely pathetic.
A disgrace to the magic knights.
What'd you say?
I think I will kill you now.
Finral is one of the nicest people I've ever met!
He's a true magic knight!
You're the failure!
You don't deserve the title no matter how strong you are!
You will regret those words.
Fool.
You may have lucked out and failed upward to get to this point.
But you're still a nobody who's talking to someone completely out of your league.
Wizard King.
Before the next teams face off against each other, allow me to put these Black Bulls in their rightful place.
In fact, the fight can start now!
Watch out!
You will!
Let the semi-finals begin!
What did you do?
Asta, wait!
Vice Captain Longris always did have an overly aggressive streak in him.
But I'm afraid this goes beyond the pale.
True, it's very strange.
But what's next?
Wizard King, sir.
You're not going to stop them?
If this were an actual battle, no one would be able to control when the fighting begins or ends.
So we'll proceed.
You were with him that day as well.
Even then I didn't like you.
From the moment I met you, the Black Bulls are the weakest of the Magic Knight Squad.
And you're the worst of them!
Asta!
Trust me, I think the same thing about you!
We're about to show you what the weakest squad is capable of!
Time-binding magic. My chronostasis.
Now then, you can both hear me.
As much as I'd like you to fight as though you were in a real battle, this is still just a tournament match. Take a moment. A long one.
Meanwhile, we'll arrange the next match. Don't worry, everything will be set up before the fervor dies down.
Prepare for the semi-final match, and we'll be needing new crystals.
Sir, yes sir!
In the meantime, gather up the other members from teams B and G, Cub.
Yes, of course sir!
Of course, any course sir!
And that's…
You'll need to grab Zergs Lubner from Team B, and that's…
And then, we'll need to grab Zergs Lubner from Team B, and we'll need to go to the next battle.
And then, we'll need to take a moment. We'll need to take a moment. A long one.
Meanwhile, we'll arrange the next match.
Don't worry, everything will be set up before the fervor dies down.
Prepare for the semi-final match, and we'll be needing new crystals.
Sir, yes sir!
You'll need to grab Zergs Lubner from Team B, and Mimosa Vermillion.
Team G is missing Fragil Tormenta, and Seke Bronzatsa.
Now then, what do you think's a fitting reward to thank you for interrupting my prime time?
Uh, no need. It was my pleasure.
Don't be shy.
Excuse me, anyone there?
Dark magic.
Dimension Slash!
What have I gotten myself into?
This pulse is weakening.
Keep trying.
You are not going to die on my watch.
Yeah, and whenever you do die, it'll be because I killed you, got it?
Put a fire in your belly and wake up!
It's all right.
If you don't wake up soon, you won't be able to eat any more yummy goodies ever again!
I can't believe this is what it's come to.
Truly terrible.
Prove you're a good rival, Asta, and win this!
Everybody step out of the portal!
This is weird. I thought we won!
What's going on?
I'm not sure.
Hold up. Why are those two fighting?
There's a crystal at each opponent's starting position for the semi-final match between Team B and Team G.
What? We're starting it already?
It bears repeating that this is simply a tournament match, not an actual fight. Your goal is to smash the other team's crystal, not to injure, maim, or kill anyone on the battlefield.
Best of luck to both teams.
Sorry, you guys. Really. I kind of got us into a mess. I just want to beat him, something that doesn't matter.
This is the final match between Team B and Team G.
What? We're starting it already?
It bears repeating that this is simply a tournament match, not an actual fight. Your goal is to smash the other team's crystal, not to injure, maim, or kill anyone on the battlefield.
Best of luck to both teams.
I'm sorry, you guys. Really. That kind of got us into a mess. I just want to beat him.
beat him so badly please help me do that of course something isn't right with long
gris he seems so what's funny you're seriously pulling us into this because
you're mad at another magic night have you lost your mind or are you just an
idiot say what sure why not that guy doesn't stand a chance against our team
if we go at them so let's win this match you're rotten runt
long gris I feel like I missed something what happened while we were gone shut
up haha is that how you talk to your teammates well
worry not this time around my magic will easily best they don't need nothing but
weaklings everywhere I turn I'll show you how extraordinary I am and I promise you
won't ever forget it
and voluntary betrayal that's right judging by the look of things I believe
someone within our ranks is unwittingly cooperating with the eye of the midnight
Sun the most likely candidate would be one of the members of the magic Knights I'm
not sure what you're saying are they being controlled by magic maybe I can't
be certain I suppose it could be magic but then whose is it he may be
distractible and constantly running off in search of interesting magic but his
intuition is usually spot-on that means something is definitely amiss the Royal
Knights selection exam will be the perfect opportunity for us to uncover this
unwitting traitor before the situation spirals out of hand when you put your
own mana on the field in order to face off against powerful opponents you end up
revealing your true nature in the process that sounds dangerous it is but we'll
do it
could it be long grass is he the one who doesn't realize he's betraying us if
that's the case we'll take our crystal with us and protect it while we head for
theirs the same way we won the first round mimosa can you handle transport duty
on it we'll need you to cover us there's been a slight change in the sequence of events
semifinals match one team B is zerk's mimosa and Asta team G is longris for Giel and Seke begin
us this team is already on the move if I'm not careful that anti-magic sword will destroy our
crystal in a single blow which means the best strategy is to destroy him and his crystal all
in this whole match now before they ever get an attack in
fight through these blasts just fine since they don't disappear at the last second like
magnus did but then there's a lot of them
that's cute but there's no way her recovery spells can keep up with my attacks
it would be easier if you gave up already Asta's fighting his butt off out there you better fight
just as hard or you'll look like a fool I'm telling you that coward isn't fit to fight much
less be a magic knight I'm the superior brother in every possible way someone who'd abandoned his
countrymen so easily as no knight well too bad I suppose they'll have to make the ultimate
sacrifice for their country you don't seem to get it Finral's only ever used his magic to help
people he's a real hero the complete opposite of you you think something like that could be
praise that just means he never learned to defeat his foes that's not something to be proud of it
shows how weak he is
Austin no not good respect the mage who keeps on winning until the end
he's the one who's doing everything right
you think so well that's great it means I'm doing everything right
I'm gonna beat you Longris for Finral's sake don't be ridiculous
Asta look out
don't give up yet it's not over
Asta
this isn't a tournament match not anymore
what do you think will come from this fight what's your plan wizard king
my recovery magic isn't fast enough
you can't keep taking damage from his attack
Asta at this rate your body will give out before the crystal does
not yet
sharp pains in my muscles and bones
that's the feeling I was waiting for
my cool down period's over
right now I can only harness this dark power two times a day
I was gonna bust it out the second time for my showdown with Yuno
but I can't wait that long
thing is
I need to concentrate and get my key flowing before I can actually use it
and I don't see that happening right now
not with him on my tail
so
how about some help Zerks
you moron
don't tell me what to do
perfect timing
I'm only doing this because I really don't like that guy
look at him
smirking with all the confidence in the world
damn it
Zora
hey kid
I'm home
where are you
I'm right in front of you dad
so have you been behaving today
whoa
the house looks amazing
nice work
thanks for cleaning up as always kiddo
dad was always the cheerful type
what stinks
he loved playing pranks on me
gotcha
you fell for it
he laughed all the time
like he was a child
ta-da
this is Zora the super mage
herald of justice
it's what now
he's a doll
I made it for you myself
yeah
I can totally tell
sure
he may be a little rough around the edges
but the important thing is that he's a man of his word
a warrior who's secretly protecting his country
that's pretty cool huh
right
yeah
I do realize I'm only 12 years old
I'm just looking toward the future
for now
you should really start talking to others more
and learn to communicate with the people around you
yeah
sure
right then
I'm off to keep the peace for another fine day
Zora was the first commoner to become a magic knight
he took the entrance exam when he was 15
but failed every time he attempted it
even fatherhood didn't deter him
but instead lit a fire under Zora
as he bolstered his efforts to pass
his diligence impressed his son
who watched his father with profound respect
and when his father did finally become a magic knight
there was no one prouder
I fought alongside a real tough character on the battlefield today
he definitely knew impressive ways to use time magic
the guy's on his way to the top that's for sure
I can't believe I get to protect our nation and its people
besides someone so good
man the magic knights are everything I'd hoped they'd be
we trust each other like lifelong friends
and face death together every day
I swear I'll use the power I possess
and protect everyone who needs my help
that's my duty as a magic knight
why'd you have to go and die
how are you gonna protect anything now
huh dad
those cows
they're magic knights
purple orcas
they must be friends of dads who came to pay their respects
alas
poor Zara Ideale
nothing but a commoner who was constantly getting in the way on the battlefield
no wonder a squad mate shot him in the back
ah well
that's what he gets for trying to pal around with nobles
who actually deserve to be magic knights
he was so tragically desperate to save yokels
life will be far easier without this scum around
true
if he's underground he can't make us look bad
what a sorry excuse for a vip room
don't you know how you should treat magic knights
now bring us your most expensive booze quick
but sir you
what is there a problem
you think you're too good to serve us or something
of course not
it's just
a cocky girl like you is just begging to be punished
please sir
i didn't mean to offend you
hey good idea
she'll make a fine snack to go along with our drinks
ah hello there mighty magic knights
i'd apologize for interrupting but it's why i'm here
who are you
what do you want freak
just try to arrest me for obstructing official business
you jerks
no more
you'll earn respect
you'll pay for your sins
i'll make sure of it
please sir my granddaughter from poway village
i understand you've taken her away but she has a return to us
we miss her dearly
please give her back to our family
sir zirks has just returned from an exhausting expedition
go home and don't come back
i beg you
please sir magic knight i beg of you
you jerks
you have such little life left in you
why not die beautifully with the help of my magic
do not dare defy the great captain of the purple orcas
the saint of pure ice
and who might you be
you will pay
you jerks
my father knew what a knight should be
and you were no magic knight
you
Are you doing so it's all the way boundaries
Now you can see anyaler
Anyone still facing the wonder
Without you
Or even sollte
Yet you're looking over
This day
It's all about
Black dazu
Little
Is
Encog A
Oh
Clower Clips
What is prime time?
Prime time.
Prime time is an extremely precious time.
Prime time I can't do without.
If anyone interrupts my most treasured moments,
they regret it.
So be careful, everyone.
La la la la.
Next time we'll deliver a bountiful belly full of plentiful platters
piled to the sky.
Black Clover, page 82.
Clover Clips, the Nightmares Charly Special.
My magic is a bottomless appetite.